A Guide to the John A. Pino papers FA1301
Rockefeller Archive Center
John A. Pino papers
1950-2001
Rockefeller Archive Center
Pino, John
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1301
7.56 Cubic Feet 5 letter document containers, 6 legal document container, 1 half-legal document container, 1 half-letter document container, 1 Paige box of photographs, and an oversize materials box
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This material was transferred to the RAC by John A. Pino in 2012 and ingested by RAC as Accession 2012:067.
Separated Materials
Special format items have been separated from the body of the collection and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
The John A. Pino papers are arranged into five series reflecting Pino's original arrangement and the years he held leadership positions in agricultural organizations:
1. International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) 1981-2000 2. Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA), 1986-1997 3. National Bureau of Animal Genetic Resources (NGABR), 1987-1996 4. Rockefeller Foundation and Rutgers Poultry Projects, 1950-1983 5. National Research Council, Board on Agriculture, and Inter-American Development Bank (IDB), 1984-2001
Scope and Contents
The John A. Pino papers contain correspondence, reports, photographs, clippings, publications, meeting minutes, bulletins, and notes related to Pino's more than 50-year career in international agricultural research and development.
Biographical / Historical
John A. Pino earned a BS in Agriculture in 1947 and PhD in Zoology in 1951 from Rutgers University. He was an associate professor and conducted research in the Department of Poultry Science at Rutgers until 1955 when he accepted an animal scientist position with the Rockefeller Foundation's Mexican Agricultural Program. In 1960, Pino became director of the program and later transferred to the Foundation's headquarters in New York to become director of the Agricultural Science Program in 1970. He retired from the Rockefeller Foundation in 1983 to serve as Agricultural Science Advisor to the Inter-American Development Bank until 1986. Dr. Pino served as a member of the National Research Council's Board on Agriculture from 1973-1977 and again beginning in 1983. He became a senior fellow of the National Research Council in 1986. Pino also served as Executive Director of CILCA, the International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs, which provided low-cost assistance to rural populations in Africa, Asia, and Latin America. Beginning in 1990, Pino served as a consultant to agricultural research organizations. A leader in the Green Revolution, Pino helped lead efforts to establish the world network of International Agricultural Research Centers to improve basic food production.
Green Revolution; Rockefeller Foundation; Agriculture -- Research
- International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA), 1981-2000; 1
  - Committee Meetings and Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board Meeting, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Trip Report, Zimbabwe and Tanzania, 1991 June 6-24 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Visits to Executive Bureau, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA), 1991 July-August (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Visit to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bureau, 1991 September-October (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA), 1991 November-1992 February (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Scope and Contents
    Report regarding "Strengthening Native Artisan Women's Programmes in Cuetzalan Mexico" and notes for February 1992 Executive Committee Meeting
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA), 1991 December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA), 1992 April (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Visit To International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bureau, 1991 May (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Includes Terms of Appointment as Executive Director for John Pino (commencing June 1, 1991)
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA), 1992 June-July (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) - Diary Notes, 1992 August-September (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Trip Report to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) - Diary Notes, 1992 October (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Report of Activities - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bureau, 1992 December-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Trip Report Visit to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) and Campus Puebla del Colegio de Postgraduados documents, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Diary of John A. Pino Visit to International Bureau CILCA (IBC), 1996 January (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Diary Notes John A. Pino Visit to International Bureau CILCA (IBC), 1996 September (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Diary Travel to Mexico International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bureau, 1997 February-April (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Diary Notes, 1998 May (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Meetings with Samuel Vargas and Leobardo Jimenez
  - Diary Visit to International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Puebla, 2000 July 3-7 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Pertains to the resignation of Benjamin V. Pena and Draft of Long Term Strategy for CILCA Programme
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mexico Symposium - "International Workshop on Sustainable Agriculture", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Mali Workshop, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Expense Records, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Many documents regarding long-distance phone conversations
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Faxes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Faxes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Faxes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Faxes, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Faxes, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Faxes, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletins, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Rural Development Programs, 1989-1998 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Philosophy, Brochures, and Manual for Producers and Technicians, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) - Mexico - Tentzo, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Brandeis University Workshop and Bulletin V, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin I, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin II, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin III, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin III photographs, undated; 2012:067:008; 33 photographs (Box 14, Folder 139, Item 2012:067:008)
    Separated Materials
    Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    Includes notes for placement of photos within bulletin
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin III photographs, undated; 2012:067:009; 16 photographs (Box 14, Folder 140, Item 2012:067:009)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin III, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Seven Slides of Maize, undated; 2012:067:010 (Box 14, Folder 141, Item 2012:067:010)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin III photographs, undated; 2012:067:011; 2 Photographs (Box 14, Folder 142, Item 2012:067:011)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Pictures for International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV, undated; 2012:067:012; 6 photographs (Box 14, Folder 143, Item 2012:067:012)
    Some photos taken in Sri Lanka
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV photographs, 1988 August; 2012:067:013; 33 photographs (Box 14, Folder 144, Item 2012:067:013)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV negatives, undated; 2012:067:014; 7 negative strips (Box 14, Folder 145, Item 2012:067:014)
  - Mali photographs, International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV, 1994; 2012:067:015; 27 photographs (Box 14, Folder 146, Item 2012:067:015)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Puno Project Photographs, 1992 September; 2012:067:016; 9 photographs (Box 14, Folder 147, Folder 2012:067:016)
    Descriptions with numbers that correspond to numbers on the back of individual photographs are typed on two sheets of paper
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV photographs, undated; 2012:067:017; 9 photographs, arrived in envelope with negatives (Box 14, Folder 148, Item 2012:067:017)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV negatives, undated; 2012:067:018; 27 negative strips, arrived in envelope with prints (Box 14, Folder 149, Item 2012:067:018)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV negatives, undated; 2012:067:019; 2 negatives (Box 15, Folder 150, Item 2012:067:019)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV slides, 1991 September; 2012:067:020; 8 slides (Box 15, Folder 151, Item 2012:067:020)
    Slides from Tecamachalco, including images of corn and crafts
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV negatives, undated; 2012:067:021; 6 negative strips (Box 15, Folder 152, Item 2012:067:021)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin IV photographs, undated; 2012:067:022; 14 photographs (Box 15, Folder 153, Item 2012:067:022)
    Wedza Project
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin V, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin V negatives, undated; 2012:067:023; 1 negative strip (Box 15, Folder 154, Item 2012:067:023)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin V photographs, 1995 October; 2012:067:024; 24 photographs (Box 15, Folder 155, Item 2012:067:024)
    Tentzo region projects, Mali Workshop,
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin VI, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin VI photographs, undated; 2012:067:025; 11 photographs (Box 15, Folder 156, Item 2012:067:025)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin VI photographs, undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Bulletin VI photographs, undated; 2012:067:026; 3 Photographs (Box 15, Folder 157, Item 2012:067:026)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) IRS Tax Exemption, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted – Financial material
  - IRS Record, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - IRS Record, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - IRS Record, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - IRS Return, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - IRS, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - IRS, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - IRS, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - IRS, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - IRS, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - IRS, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - IRS, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - IRS, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - IRS, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Projects, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Catherine Madata and Tanzania, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Biannual Report, 1992-1993, Puebla, Mexico, 1994 July 1 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Biannual Report, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    Also contains CILCA in Action, 1989-1990
  - Legal Status in Mexico, undated (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Contribution from Peruvian Children's Food Fund, 1994 August 2 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - United Nations Development Fund for Women (UNIFEM) Annual Report, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) - Tanzania photographs, undated; 2012:067:030; Re-housed into acid free folder from deteriorating binder, 8 photographs in plastic (Box 15, Folder 160, Item 2012:067:030)
    Special format items have been separated from the above listed file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
  - International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) - Cuetzalan, Mexico photographs, undated; 2012:067:031; Re-housed into acid free folder from deteriorating binder, 27 photographs in plastic (Box 15, Folder 161, Item 2012:067:031)
- Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA), 1986-1997; 2
  - Report and Correspondence Regarding Possible Service Functions of the Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA) to Inter-American Development Bank (BID), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    Correspondence with Jose Soto Angli
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA) Review Team, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA) Bolivia, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    Includes International Workshop on the Andean Agroecosystem: Synopsis, Conclusions, and Recommendations, Lima, March 30-April 2, 1992
  - G-6 Report, 1993 April (Box 4, Folder 39)
    Report of the Group of Six Experts on Its Evaluation of the Medium Term Plan 1987-1993 And Recommendations on the Preparation of the Plan for 1994-1997; Prepared in accordance with Resolution IICA/JIA/Res. 168 (V-0/89), adopted by the Inter-American Board of Agriculture in San Jose, Costa Rica, October 1989, and Resolution IICA/CE/Res.140 (X-0/90). Adopted by the Executive Committee in August 1990
  - International Board of Plant Genetic Resources (IBDGR), Bogota, 1992 March (Box 4, Folder 40)
    Propuesta para la creacion de la red Andina de recursos Fitogeneticos
  - Andean Crops - Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    Andean Roots and Tubers: Research Priorities for a Neglected Food Resource, Michael Hermann 1992; Feasibility of Establishing An International Center For Quinua and Andean Crops (Report Prepared for IICA/Bolivia) 1990; Centro de Investigacion Y Transferencia de Technologia Para Ecosistemas Fragiles Alto-Andinos June 1992
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA) Andean Center Correspondence, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - International Board of Plant Genetic Resources (IBDGR) - Propuesta Para La Creacion de la Red MesoAmericana de Recursos Fitogeneticos (Remerfi), San Jose, Costa Rica, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Keystone Dialogue, 1986-1992 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    Keystone International Dialogue Series on Plant Genetic Resources, Oslo Plenary Session, Final Consensus Report: Global Initiative for the Security and Sustainable Use of Plant Genetics Resources
  - Keystone International Dialogue on Plant Genetic Resources, Madras, India, Group Photograph, 1990 January 29-February 2; 2012:067:001 (Box 14, Folder 133, Item 2012:067:001)
  - Caribbean Agricultural Research and Development Institute (CARDI) External Review, 1991 October (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA) - Ministero da Agricultura e Reforma Agraria Visitante Data, 1993 March 25 (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture (IICA), 1997 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Keystone International Dialogue Group Photograph, Oslo, Norway, 1991 May 31-June 4; 2012:067:052 (Box 18, Folder 187, Item 2012:067:052)
    Existence and Location of Copies
- National Bureau of Animal Genetic Resources (NGABR), 1987-1996; 3
  - National Bureau of Animal Genetic Resources (NBAGR) Team Visit to U.S., 1991 January 2-22 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Winrock International, United States Agency for International Development Agriculture Support Service Project, India, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Seed Unit Study Report, Cali, Colombia, 1987 February 20 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT)
  - Development of the National Bureau of Animal Genetic Resources (NBAGR) - Report, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Report of the USAID Design Team for the Development of NBAGR for Conservation, Evaluation, Utilization, and Management of Indigenous Livestock Genetics Resources of India, John A. Pino, Keith E. Gregory, and G. Eric Bradford, Submitted to Winrock International [USAID Agricultural Research Project, New Delhi, March 8, 1992
  - India Gene Bank Dedication - Invitations, Programs, and Newsletters, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Status Paper on Conservation, Evaluation and Management of Indigenous Livestock Genetic Resources of India, Diversity, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    Contains correspondence, drafts, and final versions
  - Winrock International Assignment and International Liaison Committee for Food Corps Programs (CILCA) Mission to Sri Lanka, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Gene Bank Center photographs, India, undated; 2012:067:057; Photographs (Box 18, Folder 192, Item 2012:067:057)
- Rockefeller Foundation and Rutgers Poultry Projects, 1950-1983; 4
  - China Germplasm Conservation and Use in China: With Special Reference to a National Plant Genetic Resources Center, Rockefeller Foundation Team, 1980 November (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - China Germplasm Conservation and Use in China: With Special Reference to a National Plant Genetic Resources Center, Rockefeller Foundation Team, 1980 November (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Map of China, undated; 2012:067:002 (Folder 120, Item 2012:067:002)
  - Photograph - 6 Men Sitting, undated; 2012:067:003; Photograph (Box 14, Folder 134, Item 2012:067:003)
  - Photograph - 5 Men Walking, undated; 2012:067:004; Photograph (Box 14, Folder 135, Item 2012:067:004)
  - Photograph - 4 Men Having Tea, undated; 2012:067:005; Photograph (Box 14, Folder 136, Item 2012:067:005)
  - Photograph - 2 Men Shaking Hands, undated; 2012:067:006 (Box 14, Folder 137, Item 2012:067:006)
  - Photograph - Group Shot of 16 Men, undated; 2012:067:007 (Box 14, Folder 138, Item 2012:067:007)
  - El Cuidado y Manejo del Huevo en la Granja, undated (Box 9, Folder 103)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Egg Project photographs, Puebla, Mexico, 2017:067:029 (Box 15, Folder 159, Item 2017:067:029)
  - Projection of the Animal Sciences Programs of the Rockefeller Foundation, Drafts, 1965-1970 (Box 9, Folder 104)
  - Transition in Livestock Production in Latin America, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 105)
  - Pigmentation Reference, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Projection of the Animal Sciences Programs of the Rockefeller Foundation - Original, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Publications, Miscellaneous, 1959-1967 (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Central American Research Programs, 1978-1992 (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Report of the US Presidential Task Force to Peru, 1982 April; Bound Volume (Box 11, Folder 113)
    Inscribed by Clayton Yeutter, leader of the task force
  - Pictorial Activities, 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    Includes Rancho Experimental La Campana XV Aniversario materials, Agribusiness Council materials, clippings related to the Rockefeller Foundation's agricultural program, Community Conference on Food and Population materials sponsored by the United Nations Association, and programs from conferences.
  - Pictorial Activities photographs, 1972-1975; 2012:067:032 (Box 15, Folder 162, Item 2012:067:032)
    Contains photographs documenting visit to the International Center for Tropical Agriculture (CIAT), CIAT dedication, clippings, American Phytopathological Society, Trade Advisory Committee (TAC), and World Bank 1974
  - Cooperatives in El Salvador, 1972 February; Re-housed into acid free folder from deteriorating binder (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Cooperatives in El Salvador photographs, 1972 February 9; 2012:067:033 (Box 15, Folder 163, Item 2012:067:033)
  - Papers and Publications by John A. Pino, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Papers and Publications by John A. Pino, 1956-1960 (Box 12, Folder 117)
  - Poultry Science, 1952 November; Publication (Box 12, Folder 118)
  - Publications, 1950-1962 (Box 12, Folder 119)
  - Publications, 1954-1955; Re-housed into acid free folder from deteriorating binder (Box 12, Folder 120)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Seminar Participants, Williamsburg, Virginia, photographs, 1979 November 18-21; 2012:067:034 (Box 16, Folder 164, Item 2012:067:034)
  - Trinational Animal Health Research Project (TAHRP) IV Workshop, undated; 2017:067:035; Re-housed into acid free folder from deteriorating binder (Box 16, Folder 165, Item 2012:067:035)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Staff Seminar Photograph, Williamsburg, Virginia, 1979 November; 2012:067:036 (Box 16, Folder 166, Item 2012:067:036)
  - Nigeria Photos, undated; 2012:067:037 (Box 16, Folder 167, Item 2012:067:037)
  - Clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 125)
    Also contains International Conference on Malaria and Babesiosis Certificate, Mexico City, 1979
  - Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT) International Center for Tropical Agriculture - Colombia photograph, 1979 May; 2012:067:038 (Box 16, Folder 168, Item 2012:067:038)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - Rockefeller Foundation China photographs (with Clarence Gray), 1980; 2012:067:039 (Box 16, Folder 169, Item 2012:067:039)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Bellagio Study and Conference Center: Preparing Professional Staff for National Agriculture Programs, 1979 February 16-21; 2012:067:040 (Box 16, Folder 170, Item 2012:067:040)